craffts.com 2012-10-03

# Privacy Policy - Craffts

Subject to the other terms of the User agreement, we will not share your personal information with third parties without your consent. We will only use your information for providing the services, the delivery of goods, or any matters related to promotions offered by us. If you do not wish that we should use your information in the manner listed above please inform us by email at [info@craffts.com](mailto:info@craffts.com)

We may however provide your personal information to the vendors, dealers, manufacturers, distributors, logistics partners and other associates to provide you the service under this agreement. 

We collect your personal information when you register yourself as a member/user of our website. By submitting your details you agree to receive promotional marketing messages including but not limited to newsletters, SMS, mailers from the company, its different trading styles, business associates, partners, group companies, affiliates and third parties regarding their products/services which may be of interest to you. If you do not wish to receive such promotional marketing messages then kindly email us at [info@craffts.com](mailto:info@craffts.com)

We make good faith efforts to provide you access to your personal information upon request and to let you correct such data if it is inaccurate and amend it, when reasonably possible. 

We shall take all precautionary measures including operational as well as technical to avoid any failure, loss or misuse of any personal data. We store all information you provide on our firewall protected secure servers. 

We may disclose your personal information to any governmental, administrative, regulatory or judicial authority as and when required under law, in cases where it is obligatory to do so. Further, we can (and you authorize us to) disclose your details in reference to any complaint received against you regarding your use/misuse of the website, as we in our sole discretion believe necessary or appropriate in connection with an investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringement, piracy, or other unlawful activity. 

You automatically consent to our collection, usage and disclosure of your information by using and continuing to use this website. In case you do not agree to such collection, usage or disclosure, you may simply stop using the website. If you have any enquiry, suggestions or feedback, you may contact us at [ info@craffts.com](mailto:info@craffts.com).
